Hello.
Welcome back.
Yes, you may be wondering why the window looks different.
OK, so this is a project built in called MBK, MBK five, call you Vision five.
And this follows the arm, the directive for Mott's for the assembler.
You would see that the arm, the symbolic names are assigned differently.
And the directives we have here are different as well.
And over here, the main we use on the school, on the school main we don't use simply made.
And we know why that is, is because when we go to the reset handler, if we come over here and we search
reset Honolua oh, just give a quick overview.
I'm not here to talk at all.
Empty caber.
I cannot help it.
I have to explain every single thing.
Control F or search for a reset handler.
Okay.
And then I'll hit.
So with this the resets on like you hit enter twice it will bring you here.
You see its notes on the school on this.
Call me.
So the starting point is on the school, on this.
That is why in Karl MBK, when we export we stalwarts under squanders called Main.
Okay.
In in SDM 32 Kubi the e the application starting point is simply made without.
On the school.
Okay, so what we're going to do in this project is just copy everything in the column decayed and pasted
into a what is the embedded to Keep Idee project and start changing it life into a cube IDA format.
So that's now when you have a project created in column decay you can do to change yourself.
And it's as if you've got two items for the prize of one, you know.
So let's go ahead and do that.
I'm going to create a new project to minimize this.
I'll come over here for you.
Estimated to project and it's going to load up the target select to.
It's loaded.
Okay, I'm gonna set my microcontroller.
I'm gonna search it, ASTM 32 for one one
and, um, I'll get it.
I'll click next to grab it.
Next over here, I'll give the project a name, g.P.
Assembly, call this MBK versus KCC.
Call to versus GCSE.
Okay, does a descriptive name.
You can name it whatever you want.
I should point that out and then I'll say next and then finish.
And.
I've actually see.
Remember my decision?
Don't ask me this again, so click that.
Okay.
So it would open in a number of seconds.
Right.
It's done.
Open and close this.
This is from the previous project to close this.
Do you want to save changes?
I think.
Yes.
And so does the previous project.
Does the new one column ticket versus GCSE.
And then in the previous one, we said we were going to delete everything in this folder and see what
we get.
So we can do that.
And this project would delete everything here because we don't need these files.
I'm going to delete them.
Let's see what I can use, shift, select all of them.
And then I'm simply going to delete everything from the source folder.
I mean, call source.
And then I'm deleting everything because we write an assembly code.
Right.
The only thing we need is this over here.
Is this dot s file from the start up folder.
So now I will call source for this empty.
I'm going to right.
Click near file and then I'll call.
This may not.
S
main dot s like this finish.
Okay.
So I'm going to go to our walk, call you vision and then control A and then control C to copy of Copied
Everything or paste over here.
And this what we have.
Okay.
That's a lot of work here.
So this project, this project I've not spoken about this project.
This project is inputs and outputs.
This project.
This is just like the one we did 10 in DLT on, except that this one allows you to press the push button
and when you press the push button, you get to 10 on the LCD and turn it off.
So we're going to start off.
I'll comment everything out.
I start over here and then it's horrible, the
control V to paced and then I'll come over here.
I'll control it.
There should be a way to come in the block.
Right.
Click and then.
See?
I'll come to edit to see if I can find comment block over here.
So there's an option here on the source that should be Torgau comment, but it's deactivated.
I don't know what it is because it cannot identify this for assembly in a way.
OK.
We're going to comment that one by one.
So when we write the GCSE version of a particular line, then we comment it out.
So we're going to take this this first one RACC base.
Could you try to change this into the GCSE format by yourself in C?
OK, so to change this, we know what to do.
I'm going to copy the same name here and then we said we use DOT EKU you here.
The format is not EKU you.
And then this is the name and then comma.
This is the value we want to give to this name.
OK?
Right.
So this becomes the new value.
So then this also we know what to do, dot EKU, you know, and then we fetch this name and then comma.
Does the value we want to give it.
OK.
This we know what to do.
Comment to tell.
And then we see dot eku you.
This is the name comma.
There's the value.
We want to give it.
OK.
So I'm going to post the video.
Incomplete the rest cause this is repetitive.
And you can do it.
You know, you can try to do it yourself and compare to compare it with the outcome I get.
So.
Right.
I've changed the format of the symbolic names.
Yeah.
It took me about three to four minutes.
OK.
So this is it.
We have all of them.
I've kept the original call you efficient code in comment form.
And when I touch the project to the to the video lesson, I'm going to attach the original call.
You call your vision project as well.
So that if you have a call you vision installed, you can try both.
So it's all being commented out.
Right.
And then we've used the format.
Next then we have to do is so directive.
So over here.
Yeah.
Two extra directives.
We have to include the DOT C.P.U directive.
I'll come to the top of the fault here.
Dot c.p.u.
And then I'll give the name of our is the cortex M4.
And then the Syntex we use in Syntex.
We use it a unified.
OK.
So once that is done we come down here and this is where we continue.
Over here, the directive here.
All of this has to change.
This is the call your vision directive.
We can indicate thumb if we want to indicate that we're using thumb.
This we simply do dot thumb.
And we don't have to indicate on entry point yet.
The word export becomes.
Global without un, a global in this area.
Here is what we would call section Dotts section, but section like this.
And then the section is dot text to indicators for it for for code.
And this thumb is not even compulsory.
So we can take it out.
So after we've done this, everything looks good.
And then there is one last directive.
Over here we can align if we want, but we will skip that.
And the end directive becomes thought.
End like this.
OK.
So after we've done this, let's build and see what errors we have.
Click over here to build.
It's Beurden.
We have 12 arrows.
OK, so the reason we would have the arrows is even I forgot.
So.
OK.
This man has to change.
Remember, we pointed out that the reset handler looks for Maine and the Maine doesn't include underscore
so Maine house to be written like this.
A man has to be written like this.
And another difference is that in calling vision, when we write labels, we don't.
Let's see.
Should I wait?
The reason I'm holding back is I just deleted the stuff.
I said I was gonna keep it without deleting it.
Mm hmm.
Okay.
I'm going to control easy and just not delete and keep.
Just bear with me.
I think this will make your revision easier.
So we said this comment, this out, this we don't need us.
Well, and this part does says this, but does this export?
This becomes Dotts global dot.
Global without on a global, and the name should be main course, they reset.
Handler looks for Maine and this bar does this area.
We said we call this DOT section in our assembler over here dot section.
And then this section distorts text remains the same.
So we see a dot text over here.
OK, so this is where we end up with from this site or just a line the old guys together.
OK.
This is what it came with.
This is all new stuff.
OK.
So because this is the global label here has to be made.
And one other thing over here, over here in in the GCSE assembler, when you write a label, you've
got to put a call on there.
So everywhere we see a label, we've got to put a call on, put a call on here and then a call on here
and then a call on here.
Call on here.
And then this, a line.
We said we can keep it out or we can use dots, a line.
I thing there's a directive dot a line.
And this end is dot end in our GCSE.
Like this.
And one last thing.
Over here in our assembler, we use Slusher Losh for comment.
We don't use semicolons in call assembler.
We use semicolons to indicate comment.
Over here we don't.
So the comment I don't need to keep them there seems to.
Oh, just fix the comment without preserve in its initial format.
Right.
Do we have any more comment?
We do not.
OK.
We have some over here.
Do we have any more.
We do not.
Do we.
OK, so now let's see what we've got.
Click over here.
It's Beurden.
We've got two arrows.
Okay, so safe.
Let's see one arrow from her.
To fuse Europe?
Yes, it's OK.
It's in this function.
OK.
This will have to do with our starting point.
So let's go and look out to was starting point to the global main and then section is the text.
And then we have our main over here.
Then we have our branch over here.
And then what do we not have we have everything we need.
And then let's see C.P.U Coatex him for.
It should be fine.
OK.
I know what is happening.
So you remember the files were deleted when we started.
Our main had a lot of files.
One of such files or one of those files is the um is the system in its file.
And this subroutine loops to that.
There's a system in it.
So I'm just gonna copied from a previous project.
If we go to this over here, if we go and find our loop fields, you, VSS should be down here.
This is research handler.
It brings us here.
And then it jumps over here.
And then it goes to loop fills you OBSS loop fields you OBSS require a system in IT system and it's
existed in one of the files were deleted.
So I'm gonna go to our board GPO Assembly project, go to core and then copy the system.
And it's the.
I'm going to copy these three files system as dictated to X X, but see, I think its counterpart is
the.
There's this one here.
I think it would have been better if the guys at S.T. put these false in the setup so that we wouldn't
need to find it in our application source files.
In a way, I'm going to start off by copying these three.
I think these three should be required.
So.
Right, click copy and then I'll come to our new project.
This is our new project, GPL, your assembly CO, MBK versus GCSE in our source forward.
All right, click.
And then I'll paste on exist here.
Let's build and see.
Click over here.
OK.
The arrow disappeared.
No, we've got no warning.
Um, I'm sure we just need one of the three, but we have the three.
We can keep the three.
If you are more curious, you can go delete.
And the other two deleted two at random and see who has the system in it.
Right.
But we're moving on.
Okay, so, Nonno, we've downloaded Anana with boats.
Let's go to the debugger.
I'll click over here.
So like this.
And then.
Okay.
And then I'll say, okay from here.
OK.
It's done.
So we can run our code.
It's done case.
They're working.
Okay, so click here to run and it's run in.
But when I pressed my board.
Nothing happens.
Uh, no, I was pressing the wrong key.
When I pressed that, it was pressed the, um.
The black button.
Sorry.
Bother when I press, as you can see where my hand is on it.
The lid is on when I lift my only gross off where my hand is on its own.
When I lived on my own, it goes off.
So this is how we can convert.
Call your vision assembly project to our cube IDC assembly project.
And this same project should work in any form of GCSE assembly project.
So if you are a Clipse GCSE assembler, they should be able to work.
They use the same syntax.
So that's all the rest.
If you have any questions or talk, just live in the questions and answers.
I really feel fine and of course, useful.
Take some time off to leave.
I review.
And have a beautiful day.
I shall see you later.